So, our next topic today is
about HDFC Ergo's Optima Restore Health Insurance Plan
versus ICICI Bank's Health Security. We will
give you a comparison of these two products so that you can select a good
health insurance for yourself. We
subscribe to both of them. If you have
not seen this video, the link is
in the description, you can watch it. First, let's
talk about the companies. Both the companies
are very big companies in themselves and the service is very good.
Both the companies have very good claim settlement ratios. If we
talk about the product, then
in this number 8, the upper hospitalization is
30 days and post hospitalization is
60-day subscription and 180 abs moments are
covered in both the companies. If you
subscribe, then you can get 2 years'
subscription for Ayurvedic treatment in ICICI Bank
and the condition in it is that it should be a
government hospital, it should be a government
approved center. When
Ayurvedic treatment is not covered in the school, if we
talk about these donor expenses, then it
is covered in both the companies, but ICICI Bank
In Lombard, this is Over End Absorption in
Cover, which means that apart from yours, it will also be given
to your company for additional benefit. For example,
if you subscribe and the
company spends Rs. 15 lakhs on your channel, which you subscribe for Rs. 5, on
this condition, this can be two
lakhs and this is the maximum limit, it can be up to Rs.
10 lakhs, when you go to school, this can
now be a screenshot, but now you will not have to
go to office, due to these injuries, it will be
edited in this, if we talk about air ambulance, then
in ICICI Lombard, there is Over
End Absorption in Cover, for example, if you are a
serviceman and you need an ambulance, then
subscribe, this is your exit subscription,
which will be for a maximum time, and if we
talk about your research benefits, then this long
ribbon benefit is unlimited time, if you
subscribe, then as soon as this period
ends, you
can reset it unlimited times, on the condition that it does
not give coverage to remedies, if we
talk about restoration of such categories, then  Restoration will be available
and now you can get treatment in this on the condition that
when will you get it on re-admission.
Talking about the hospital panel, then subscribe to 5000 hospitals in this,
it means that if the policy holder is
not able to go to the hospital due to some reason, it
is not available in the hospital, then the
policy holder can get
treatment done from his home, which
is covered in both the companies. MCB means no
claim bonus. ICICI Lombard, it is 10
percent, which is a maximum of 50%
cover. This subscription is 50% in a year, that is,
if you do not subscribe,
for example, if you have subscribed, you
can purchase it additionally in this ward. You have to subscribe for no claim bonus,
such ghee, it
means additional
Chittor protector. If the claim on your policy is
below 50 thousand, then ICC
number does not deduct your no claim bonus.
In HDFC Ergo, this
option is available only in riders. It is an
inbuilt feature of the policy. Let's talk about this ambulance.
So one per cent of minute and
maximum Rs.10000 per hospitalization, you
can click on this number. When they
talk about 2030 in school, then
you get it in this in which their select which is
their subscription, when the school
takes the duty that you get your checkup done from anywhere
and give us the bill, we will pay you the
bills, which in a footer, in a
policy of 10 lakhs, ₹5000, this Paneer
Whistle subscribe button, if we
talk about surgery covered different styles in both the companies, then
subscribe to this number 10, so that when you
subscribe to the school child, there is
no discount on service, whereas
you get a discount of 1.5 rupees from Share Gaon, if we
talk about riders, then there is a
long director for which the
policy holder does not have to make a zoomable payment,
this is available in Idea, you
can subscribe to this and you have to subscribe
extra, this means that
whatever new items like you do not have to subscribe are
covered,
some details about both the products
People have tried to provide it, so
you can select your product as per your choice,
both are very good products, so
we keep bringing all this information about both these companies on Amazon, so
please like and subscribe to our channel,
thank you for
watching.